Division of Paleobotany Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Maps, Series I
  - Topographic Maps. United States., 000003
    - New York. Quadrangle: Goshen scale: 1:31680 Latitude/Longtitude: N4122.5-W7415/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1943; 000127
    - New York. Quadrangle: Peekamoose Mtn scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4152.5-W7422.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1943; 000134
    - New York. Quadrangle: Warwick scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4115-7415/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1943; 000156
    - New York. Quadrangle: Freehold scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4215-W7400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1943; 000165
    - New York. Quadrangle: Croton Falls scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4115-W7337.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1944; 000175
    - New York. Quadrangle: Bearsville scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4200-W7407.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1945; 000129
    - New York. Quadrangle: Woostock scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4200-W4700/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1945; 000146
    - New York. Quadrangle: Napanoch scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4200-W7400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1945; 000147
    - New York. Quadrangle: Hensonville scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4215-W7407.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1945; 000162
    - New York. Quadrangle: Ashland scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4215-7415/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1945; 000163
    - New York. Quadrangle: Prattsville scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4215-W7422.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1945; 000164
    - New York. Quadrangle: Hunter scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4207.5-W7407.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1945; 000179
    - New York. Quadrangle: Verbank scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4137.5-W7337.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1946; 000144
    - New York. Quadrangle: Cornwall scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4122.5-w7400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1946; 000148
    - New York. Quadrangle: Popolopen Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4115-W7400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1946; 000159
    - New York. Quadrangle: Kaaterskill scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4207.5-W7400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1946; 000160
    - New York. Quadrangle: Kaaterskill scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: n4207.5-w7400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1946; 000161
    - New York. Quadrangle: Stephentown Center scale: 1:31680 Latitude/Longtitude: N4320-W7322.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1947; 000124
    - New York. Quadrangle: Millbrook scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4145-W7337.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1947; 000135
    - New York. Quadrangle: Pine Plains scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4152.5-W7337.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000128
    - New York. Quadrangle: Kinderhook scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4222.5-W7337.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000119
    - New York. Quadrangle: East Chatman scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4222.5-W7330/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000120
    - New York. Quadrangle: Averill Park scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4237.5-W7330/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000123
    - New York. Quadrangle: Nassau scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4230-w7330/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000125
    - New York. Quadrangle: Ravena scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4222.5-W7345/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000126
    - New York. Quadrangle: East Greenbush scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4230-W7337.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000154
    - New York. Quadrangle: Leeds scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4215-W7352.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000166
    - New York. Quadrangle: Hudson N scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4215-W7345/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000167
    - New York. Quadrangle: Alcove scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4222.5-W7352.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000168
    - New York. Quadrangle: Delman scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4230-W7345/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000169
    - New York. Quadrangle: Delmar scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4230-W7345/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000170
    - New York. Quadrangle: Hillsdale scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4207.5-W7330/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1953; 000177
    - New York. Quadrangle: Haverstraw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4107.5-W7352.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1955; 000155
    - New York. Quadrangle: Oscawana scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4122.5-W7345/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000149
    - New York. Quadrangle: Mohegan Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4115-W7345/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000173
    - New York. Quadrangle: Walden scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4130-W7407.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000118
    - New York. Quadrangle: Newburgh scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4130-W7400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000121
    - New York. Quadrangle: West Point scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4122.5-W7352.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000150
    - New York. Quadrangle: Pleasant Valley scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4137.5-W7345/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000157
    - New York. Quadrangle: Poughkeepsie scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4137.5-W7352.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000158
    - New York. Quadrangle: Clintondale scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4137.5-W7400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000171
    - New York. Quadrangle: Gardiner scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4137.5-W7407.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000172
    - New York. Quadrangle: Peekskill scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4115-W7352.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000174
    - New York. Quadrangle: Phoenicia scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4200-W7415/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000130
    - New York. Quadrangle: Shandaken scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4200-W7422.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000131
    - New York. Quadrangle: Pine Plains scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4152.5-W7337.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000132
    - New York. Quadrangle: West Kill scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4207.5-W7422/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000176
    - New York. Quadrangle: Lexington scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4207.5-W7415/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000178
    - New York. Quadrangle: Salt Point scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4145-W7345/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000136
    - New York. Quadrangle: Hyde Park scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4145-W7352.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000141
    - New York. Quadrangle: Saugerties scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4200-W7352.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000145
    - New York. Quadrangle: Rock City scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4152.5-W7345/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000151
    - New York. Quadrangle: Kingston E scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4152.5-W7352.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1963; 000152
    - New York. Quadrangle: Kingston W scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4152.5-W7400/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000137
    - New York. Quadrangle: Ashokan scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4152.5-W7407.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000139
    - New York. Quadrangle: Mohonk Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4145-W7407.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000142
    - New York. Quadrangle: Saratoga Springs scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4300-W7345/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000117
    - New York. Quadrangle: Rondout Reservoir scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4145-W7422.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000133
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Garrison scale: 1: 62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10115/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1922; 000263
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Minot scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10115/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1928; 000407
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Coleharbor scale: 1: 62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10100/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1929; 000302
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Kongsberg scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10045/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1929; 000346
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Benedict scale: 1:625000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10100/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1929; 000491
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Dunseith scale: 1:62 500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W100100/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1939; 000561
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Aylmer scale: :1625000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10000/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1940; 000472
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Heart Butte scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10145/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1944; 000333
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Maddock scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W9930/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1945; 000197
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Turtle Lake scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10045/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1947; 000244
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sheyenne Lake scale: 1:625000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10000/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1947; 000516
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Minot NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-w10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000410
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mohall scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000412
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Tolley scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837.5-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000420
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Norwich scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000428
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Norma scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837.5-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000453
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Antler SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000460
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Burlington scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000467
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sawyer scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000526
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Surrey scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000553
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Donnybrook scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000564
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Greene scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837.5-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000183
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Grano scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000185
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Grano scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837.5-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000186
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Grano SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000187
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Granville scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000188
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Granville NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000189
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Granville NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000190
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Granville SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000191
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Washburn scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000226
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Voltaire scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000230
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Velva scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000232
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Turtle Creek NE scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10045/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000239
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hartland scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000339
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Karlsruhe NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000352
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lansford NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837.5-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000360
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lansford NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000361
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lansford SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000362
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lansford SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-w10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000363
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Landa SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000366
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Max NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000377
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Maxbass scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000378
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Deering SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000385
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mohall SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000386
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mouse River Park scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000389
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mouse River Park NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4852-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000390
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mouse River NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4852.5-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000391
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mouse River SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000392
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Carpio scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000397
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Carpio NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000398
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mohall NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4852-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000413
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Tolley SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000421
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Glenburn scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000423
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Newburg SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000447
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Bantry scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10030/7.8 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000483
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Riga scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000514
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sherwood scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4852.5-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000517
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sawyer scale: 1:625000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10100/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000525
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sawyer NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000527
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Stanton scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10115/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000529
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Simcoe scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000538
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Eckman scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000558
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Eckman SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000559
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Denbeigh scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000565
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Deering scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000568
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Deering NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000569
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Deering SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000570
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Wilton scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10045/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000213
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Willow City SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000217
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: West Hope SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000222
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Upham scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000233
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Upham SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000235
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Des Lacs scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000288
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Devils Lake scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W9845/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000289
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Renville scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000313
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Kramer scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837.5-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000344
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Karlsruhe scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000351
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lansford scale: 1:62 500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10115/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000359
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Landa scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4852.5-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000364
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mouse River Park scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4845-W10145/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000388
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Newburg scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837.5-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000445
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Newburg SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4830-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000446
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Antler NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4852.5-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000459
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Bantry NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000484
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sawyer SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000524
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sheyenne Lake NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: 47100-F1-TF-024 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000541
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Deep scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4837.5-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000566
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Deering scale: 1:625000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10100/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000567